<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Case-Study on Joni Virtanen</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/case-study/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Case-Study on Joni Virtanen</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/case-study/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Eksote</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/eksote/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/eksote/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;eksote&#34;&gt;Eksote&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;redesigning-eksotefi-website&#34;&gt;Redesigning Eksote.fi Website&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The goal of this project was to revamp the Eksote.fi website to improve user experience and address various usability issues. Key objectives included making the website more user-friendly and enhancing accessibility.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;user-interviews&#34;&gt;User interviews&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the pursuit of enhancing the Eksote website, we conducted user interviews as part of the project&amp;rsquo;s initial research phase. Our primary objective was to gain insights into user opinions and experiences with the current Eksote website. The valuable feedback obtained from these interviews served as a cornerstone throughout the entire project&amp;rsquo;s planning and design process, ensuring a user-centric approach.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>m2Kodit</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/m2kodit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/m2kodit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;m2-kodit&#34;&gt;M2-Kodit&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;usability-teting&#34;&gt;Usability teting&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The central objective of this UX research project was to ensure the usability of the M2-Kodit website from the perspectives of both current and potential residents (applicants).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary&#34;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For this project, we divided the user testing into two distinct groups: &amp;ldquo;Current Residents&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Potential Residents&amp;rdquo; of M2-Kodit. The test tasks were tailored to address the specific needs and objectives of each group.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The primary objective of the tasks assigned to the &amp;ldquo;Current Residents&amp;rdquo; group was to identify any usability issues on the website concerning the discovery and utilization of services available to individuals currently residing in M2-Kodit&amp;rsquo;s homes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mipro</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/mipro/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/mipro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;miprofi---redesign&#34;&gt;Mipro.fi - redesign&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The project aimed to modernize and revamp the visual style of an existing website to enhance its overall user experience and align it with current design trends.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;challenges&#34;&gt;Challenges&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;dl&gt;&#xA;&lt;dt&gt;&lt;em&gt;Outdated Design&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;&lt;dd&gt;The website had an outdated visual style, making it appear less appealing and user-friendly&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;&lt;dt&gt;&lt;em&gt;Brand Consistency&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;&lt;dd&gt;The challenge was to refresh the design while maintaining brand identity and recognition&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;&lt;dt&gt;&lt;em&gt;User-Centered Approach&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;&lt;dd&gt;Ensuring that the new design catered to the needs and preferences of the target audience&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;&lt;/dl&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/Error1.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omaolo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/omaolo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/omaolo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;omaolo&#34;&gt;Omaolo&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;usability-testing&#34;&gt;Usability testing&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This extensive usability testing initiative encompassed a total of three distinct tests, each conducted at various stages of the service&amp;rsquo;s development. In each test, both the customer and professional perspectives were tested. In total, the number of test participants were:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Customers: 6 + 15 + 6&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Professionals: 4 + 12 + 4&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The purpose of these usability testing projects was to uncover usability issues in omaolo.fi&amp;rsquo;s core use cases and views through usability testing. Each testing project typically focused on different use cases or views and proposed improvements for them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testi Case Study</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/bioenergia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/bioenergia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;bioenergia&#34;&gt;Bioenergia&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;web-magazine-redesign&#34;&gt;Web magazine redesign&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The goal of this project was to redesign a web magazine to provide a seamless user experience for readers who can both access free articles and place orders for the magazine. The challenge was to refresh the visual style while adhering to existing graphic guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;challenges&#34;&gt;Challenges&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;dl&gt;&#xA;&lt;dt&gt;&lt;em&gt;1. Mixed Content Access&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;&lt;dd&gt;Balancing free and premium content access for users while maintaining a clear distinction.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;&lt;dt&gt;&lt;em&gt;2. Visual Refresh&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;&lt;dd&gt;Updating the website&amp;rsquo;s visual style to make it modern and appealing while adhering to the client&amp;rsquo;s established graphic guidelines.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;&lt;dt&gt;&lt;em&gt;3. Ordering Magazine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;&lt;dd&gt;Implementing an intuitive ordering system for users interested in purchasing the magazine.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;&lt;/dl&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/Error1.png&#34; alt=&#34;alt text&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
